<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="html_header">
        <![CDATA[
        <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
        <html><head>
        <meta charset="utf-8">
        <style>
		   .leftimg {
		   	align:left;
		    float:left;
		    margin: 0px 0px 0px 0px;
		   }
		   .rightimg  {
		    float: right;  
		    margin: 7px 0 7px 7px;
		   }
	  	   body{
	  	       text-align:justify;
	  	   }
	  	    p {
    		text-indent: 35px;
   			}
	  	 </style>
	  	 </head>
	  	 ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="greeting_text" formatted="false">
        <![CDATA[
        <body style="background-color:"#FAF398">
        <font color="#3A2313">
        <b>Welcome!</b><br/><br/>This is Intergalactic Committee of Living Species Protection (aka ICLSP). Yesterday our (still unknown to you) devices made it possible to precisely calculate the end date of your colony existence.
        <br/>		<br/>
		<img src="file:///android_res/drawable/illustration_1.png" width="100%" />
	<br/>	<br/>
        You call the event \"end of the world\" or \"apocalypse\".  It's exact date is December 21, 2012 UTC Earth time. The purpose of ICLSP is to detect and protect potentially endangered forms of life.
		This program was sent to earthlings in order to save you. To get started, check out the timer, located at the top of the screen. If the numbers show that it's less than three days left - we will not help you. Do not read any more and delete the program.
		<br/>
		<br/>
		Many planets have suffered the exact same fate that will soon become your reality. We have the necessary knowledge, and we'll  share it to you. From now on you will start to receive messages. Filled with invaluable experience. 
		<br/>Or not.
		<br/><br/>
		Due to insufficient funding, ICLSP can not send more than one message per day.  Appreciate this help and maybe some of you will survive.
		<br/><br/>
		<img src="file:///android_res/drawable/illustration_2.png" width="100%" />
		<br/><br/>
		Our rescue ships are on their way. Survive the apocalypse and you will be saved.
		<br/>
		Sincerely yours, head of ICLSP.
		]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_text" formatted="false">
        <![CDATA[
        <body style="background-color:"#FAF398">
        <font color="#3A2313">
        <table>
        <tr border="1px">
        <td align="left"><img src="file:///android_res/drawable/help_hipster.png" width="80%"/></td>
        <td width="70%" padding-left="10px"><font color="#3A2313"><b>Ok, I'll explain you everything: </b><td>
		</tr>
		<table>
		<br/>
        See the <b>numbers</b> above? They are very important. They show the amount of time that your civilization have. Do not forget to keep an eye on it. 
		<br/><br/>
		When our ships will be evacuating humans, your <b>rank</b> will play a crucial role. You can see your current rank on the top panel. You can monitor the progress in achieving new ranks on the same panel.
		<br/><br/>
		<img src="file:///android_res/drawable/pogon.png" width="95%" align="center"/> 
		<br/><br/>		
		Get the experience <b>points</b> to earn new ranks. The more active you are, the more points you can get. Visit the application at least once a day, read messages, share them with friends and you will stand out! 
		<br/><br/>
		<img src="file:///android_res/drawable/points.png" width="95%" align="center" />
		<br/><br/>		
		You will receive messages from the best ICLSP experts. Their <b>faces</b> will be shown near the text.
		<br/><br/>
		<img src="file:///android_res/drawable/help_en.png" width="100%"/>
		<br/><br/>
		You are also able to see the <b>messages history</b>. It is at the bottom of the screen. It is called: \"Messages history\". \nThat's just it :) 
		]]>
    </string>

    <string-array name="messages">
        <item>|ICLSP|Welcome! \nThis is the Intergalactic Committee of Living Species Protection (aka ICLSP). Yesterday
            our (still unknown to you) devices made it possible to precisely calculate the end date of your colony
            existence.|0
        </item>
        <item>|Advice of a day|Survival preparation requires funds for survival preparation. \n Start borrowing money
            today. Borrow a lot and do it often - you’ll not have to give anything back. \n \nI.e., this application was
            created using borrowed money only. By grinding and ‘papier-mache’-ing. \n \n You will see a lesson on how to
            sew a cowards pocket (to hold all your money) in the next messages.|1
        </item>
        <item>http://bit.ly/TU4FB9|Anthropophagy|You may wonder, what are we going to feed you during the intergalactic
            flight?\n\n Basically, hope is the only thing we provide...\nWe recommend you to stock up on bags with
            cabbage and dead fish. Take any food at all. Please, ensure to be fat enough to survive.\n\nThere are also
            many other things you should take. You can see the complete list by clicking the button above. You can
            change it by adding anything you want!|2
        </item>
        <item>|A boy|We heard the story of a boy who saved himself from the storm on a desert island. \nAnd he lived
            there alone for a long time. He was sooooooooo bored that he even turned into a girl. \nAnd he was still too
            bored.\n\n You can become this “boy”, if you keep this program a secret. Don’t use this chance by your own.
            Tell your friends!|3
        </item>
        <item>http://bit.ly/Tq1sah|Lobsterz|You\'re with us for four days already! ICLSP is insincerely happy about it!
            To mark the occasion, we urge you to go to the bar this week and order three glasses of beer with lobsters.
            Lobsters are cool and we\'re almost sure that you\'ve never tried one :)|4
        </item>
        <item>http://bit.ly/W1NVp7|The list|Our engineers will prepare everything that you will need on a new planet.
            But we do not know exactly what it is. Add the names of all the things, flora and fauna, that are necessary
            for you to the list.|5
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="panic_messages">
        <item>5 hours till apocalypse. \nEverything is under control. Stay cool</item>
        <item>We\'re almost here. Time till lending:\n\n2 hours</item>
        <item>The Earth seems so small… Much smaller, than we imagined. \nBut that is good, - that means that we can
            evacuate everyone in one shot!
        </item>
        <item>This is a pilot of ICLSP spaceship. \nUnexpected error has occured. Code: \n\n ЕГГОГ 003 (wrong planet
            landing) \n\n I declare panic!
        </item>
        <item>We have a new plan. You\'ll see it soon. Everything will be clear in 7 minutes. \nWorry.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="panic_messages_btn_text">
        <item>Ok</item>
        <item>C\'mon guys</item>
        <item>Cool!</item>
        <item>\@#$%k!</item>
        <item>Oh, I do!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="apocalypse_window_text1">
        Great news! \n\nIt’s still few hours remaining till the apocalypse, and we have already saved you! As you
        already know, our plans implied evacuation of people like you - brave and insistent. \n\nHere’s a detailed
        scheme of our plan:
    </string>

    <string name="apocalypse_window_text2">
        It is obvious that the plan was developed by the best ICLSP engineers and contains no mistakes. But, as it
        usually happens, our Glorious programmers programmed an error: \n\nError 003 \n(wrong planet landing)\n\nMeanwhile you
        were preparing your stuff and looking into the sky with hope waiting for the plane. \n\nSee the photo from the
        scene, it explains everything:
    </string>

    <string name="apocalypse_window_text3">
        You may think that it’s a complete fail, but… \nThe pilot’s name is But. His parents gave him this name because
        he has to stand against any difficulties and against actually everything. So while we were developing brand new
        ideal and perfect plan, he just destroyed the danger himself. \n\nThis it:
    </string>

    <string name="apocalypse_window_text4">
        So that is all. It’s the end of a beautiful adventure which connected us. We were glad to help you. \nSee you next
        apocalypse. \n\nBye! \n\nWe’ll be glad to hear your love to us! Just drop something here:
        \n\nlutshe.studio@gmail.com
    </string>

</resources>